frenchtribune.com 2017-06-19

# Privacy Policy | French Tribune

FrenchTribune.com and its subsidiaries ("FrechTribune.com & Tribune Online Services") respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides succinctly the manner your data is collected and used by websites operated by Tribune Online Services. We request you to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. 

By accessing the services provided by FrenchTribune.com and our associated wesites (operated by Tribune Online Services group), you agree to the collection and use of your data by FrenchTribune.com in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact FrenchTribune.com Information Desk at [ft-info@frenctribune.com](mailto:ft-info@frenctribune.com) or use the contact form.

We want you to feel comfortable while using our web sites and we respect your privacy. FrenchTribune does not share your private information with third party websites.

We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs and also through services provided by internet traffic monitoring services along with computer-related information obtained 

from cookies sent to your browser from:

1 web server cookie stored on your hard drive  
2 an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use  
3 the type of computer you're using  
4 the type of web browser you're using 

For registered users, we collect email address, username and password. This information is stored in encrypted format on our secure servers.

FrenchTribune.com collects the personally identifiable information from you when you register with us. During registration you are required to give us your contact information (such as name, email address, gender and address).

Tribune Online Services respects your privacy online and we do not share any data with third party websites. We carry advertisements on our websites. These advertisements may also collect information about your IP address, Browser Type and Version.
